Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/shahshaili19 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
Algorithms
Machine Learning

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Gujarati (Native or Bilingual)
Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

How to Win a Data Science Competition: Learn from Top Kagglers Introduction to Deep Learning

Shaili Shah

Software Engineer at Google Bengaluru

Summary

Experienced Lead Data Scientist with a demonstrated history of working in the financial service industry. Skilled in Microsoft Excel, Customer Service, Microsoft Word, C++, and Artificial Intelligence (AI). Strong engineering professional with a Master's Degree focused in Computer Science from Indian Institute of Technology, Delhi.

Experience

Google Software Engineer January 2020 - Present (8 months) Bangalore

Envestnet | Yodlee Lead Data Scientist July 2018 - January 2020 (1 year 7 months) Bengaluru Area, India

FootPrints - think BEYOND
Organising Team Member
October 2012 - May 2014 (1 year 8 months)
Vadodara

Education

Indian Institute of Technology, Delhi Master's Degree, Computer Science · (2016 - 2018)

The Maharaja Sayajirao University of Baroda Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science (2012 - 2016)

Baroda Lions School High School · (2007 - 2012)